A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial records, Press Office, Series 25 FA368
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Agency and Commission Reports, 3; 13.5 Cubic Feet
  - Sports & Physical Fitness Joint Legislative Committee, March 31, 1964 (Box 66, Folder 1429)
  - Governor's Committee on Milk Marketing, April 24, 1964 (Box 66, Folder 1430)
  - New York State Liquor Authority, 1963 (Box 66, Folder 1431)
    Annual Report, April 27, 1964
  - Office of Transportation, 1963 (Box 66, Folder 1432)
    Annual Report, June 12, 1964
  - Investigation of Purchasing Practices & Procedures of Albany County, June 15, 1964 (Box 66, Folder 1433)
  - Office of Regional Development, 60 Year Development Report, June 28, 1964 (Box 66, Folder 1434)
  - Citizen's Committee on Reapportionment, November 30, 1964 (Box 66, Folder 1435)
  - Governor's Committee on Minimum Wage, December 6, 1964 (Box 66, Folder 1436)
  - Drought Survey Report: Commission on Water Resources Planning, December 15, 1964 (Box 66, Folder 1437)
  - New York Women: Committee on the Education & Employment of Women, December 19, 1964 (Box 66, Folder 1438)
  - Pure Waters, December 28, 1964 (Box 66, Folder 1439)
  - The Legislature & Higher Education in New York State, December 30, 1964 (Box 66, Folder 1440)
  - State University Construction Fund, 1964 (Box 66, Folder 1441)
    Annual Report, December 31, 1964
  - New York State Identification & Intelligence System, January 8, 1965 (Box 66, Folder 1442)
  - Bingo Control Commission, 3rd Annual Report, January 31, 1965 (Box 66, Folder 1443)
  - Long Island Railroad Report, February 25, 1965 (Box 66, Folder 1444)
  - Journey to Work Analysis re: Westchester, Putnam & Rockland Counties, March 23, 1965 (Box 66, Folder 1445)
  - Per Capita State Aid - Commission on State-Local Fiscal Relations, March 24, 1965 (Box 66, Folder 1446)
  - New York State Council on the Arts, 1965 (Box 66, Folder 1447)
    Annual Report, April 1965
  - Reapportionment Recommended by Democrats, April 1965 (Box 66, Folder 1448)
  - Loan Shark Rackets, April 1965 (Box 66, Folder 1449)
  - Governor's Committee on Hospital Costs, April 11, 1965 (Box 66, Folder 1450)
  - New York State Citizen's Committee on Welfare Costs, April 30, 1965 (Box 66, Folder 1451)
  - The Next Step - Building for Outdoor Recreation, May 15, 1965 (Box 66, Folder 1452)
  - Administration of Criminal Justice in New York State, Special Report, June 3, 1965 (Box 66, Folder 1453)
  - Investigation of Nassau County Jail Conditions, Nickerson vs. Cahn, June 26, 1965 (Box 66, Folder 1454)
  - Pollution Report of Lake Erie & Its Tributaries, July 1965 (Box 66, Folder 1455)
  - Port Authority Report re: Elimination of New York and New Jersey Sites for Jetport, July 29, 1965 (Box 67, Folder 1456)
  - Joint Legislative Committee on Natural Resources, 1965 (Box 67, Folder 1457)
    Annual Report, September, 1965
  - Data on Youth, New York State Division for Youth, September 20, 1965 (Box 67, Folder 1458)
  - Construction Report of Mental Hygiene Facilities, 1964-65, October 11, 1965 (Box 67, Folder 1459)
  - Second Report of the British Narcotics System, October 28 1965 (Box 67, Folder 1460)
  - New York State Identification & Intelligence System Fingerprint Classification, November 15, 1965 (Box 67, Folder 1461)
  - Pure Waters Program, November 16, 1965 (Box 67, Folder 1462)
  - Superintendent of Public Works Comment on the Audit Report & Allegations of Waste of Funds in the Department of Public Works, November 30, 1965 (Box 67, Folder 1463)
  - New York State Department of Public Works, 1965 (Box 67, Folder 1464)
    Annual Report Statistical Appendix, December 1965
  - Civil Defense Report Due to Blackout, December 11, 1965 (Box 67, Folder 1465)
  - Governor's Library Conference Report, December 14, 1965 (Box 67, Folder 1466)
  - New York State Teacher's Retirement System, December 28, 1965 (Box 67, Folder 1467)
  - New York State Council on Drug Addiction, December 20, 1965 (Box 67, Folder 1468)
  - New York State Liquor Authority, 1965 (Box 67, Folder 1469)
    Annual Report, December 31, 1965
  - New York State Science & Technology Foundation, 1965 (Box 67, Folder 1470)
    Annual Report, January 27, 1966
  - New York State Safety Car Program, Interim Report, January 31, 1966 (Box 67, Folder 1471)
  - Hudson River Valley Commission, January 31, 1966 (Box 67, Folder 1472)
  - Governor's Conference on Natural Beauty, February 25, 1966 (Box 67, Folder 1473)
  - Temporary Commission of Investigation, 8th Annual Report 1965, March; 1966 (Box 67, Folder 1474)
  - Governor's Committee on Public Employee Relations, Interim Report, March 3, 1966 (Box 67, Folder 1475)
  - Mental Hygiene Facilities Improvement Fund, Annual Report of the Architectural & Construction Program, March 31, 1966 (Box 67, Folder 1476)
  - Combating Organized Crime, 1965 Conference, Oyster Bay, New York, April 1966 (Box 67, Folder 1477)
  - Governor's Committee on Public Employee Relations, Final Report, April 7, 1966 (Box 67, Folder 1478)
  - Governor's Conference on Crime in New York City, April 21, 1966 (Box 67, Folder 1479)
  - Report on Consumer Borrowing, April 26, 1966 (Box 67, Folder 1480)
  - 25th Anniversary of State Aid to Housing for the Aging, April 6, 1966 (Box 67, Folder 1481)
  - Battery Park City, May 12, 1966 (Box 67, Folder 1482)
  - Tri-State Transportation Commission: 1985 An Interim Plan, May 18, 1966 (Box 67, Folder 1483)
  - Governor's Conference on Manpower Training, June 3, 1966 (Box 67, Folder 1484)
  - Susquehanna River Basin Compact, June 9, 1966 (Box 67, Folder 1485)
  - State Division of Housing & Community Renewal, 1966 (Box 67, Folder 1486)
    Annual Report, August 31, 1966
  - Office of Transportation, 1965 (Box 67, Folder 1487)
    Annual Report, September 9, 1966
  - Statewide Comprehensive Outdoor Recreation Plan, Vol. 1, September 16, 1966 (Box 67, Folder 1488)
  - Statewide Comprehensive Outdoor Recreation Plan, Vol. 1, September 16, 1966 (Box 67, Folder 1489)
  - State Department of Mental Hygiene Narcotic Addiction Program, September 19, 1966 (Box 68, Folder 1490)
  - New York State Safety Car Project, September 19, 1966 (Box 68, Folder 1491)
  - New York State Safety Car Project, September 19, 1966 (Box 68, Folder 1492)
  - Investigation of Organized Crime & Problems of Law Enforcement in Rochester, September 27, 1966 (Box 68, Folder 1493)
  - Coordinated Program for the Water Resources of New York State, October 5, 1966 (Box 68, Folder 1494)
  - Process of Combating Juvenile Delinquency & Youth, New York State Division for Youth, October 11, 1966 (Box 68, Folder 1495)
  - New York City Municipal Hospital System, Preliminary Report, October 12, 1966 (Box 68, Folder 1496)
  - Interstate 81 Near Binghamton, October 16, 1966 (Box 68, Folder 1497)
  - Management Improvement in State Government, October 22, 1966 (Box 68, Folder 1498)
  - New York State Identification & Intelligence System, A New Concept in Criminal Justice Information Sharing, November 3, 1966 (Box 68, Folder 1499)
  - New York State Identification & Intelligence System, A New Concept in Criminal Justice Information Sharing, November 3, 1966 (Box 68, Folder 1500)
  - State Consumer Services Booklet, November 16, 1966 (Box 68, Folder 1501)
  - Mayor's Task Force on Reorganization of New York City Government, December; 1966 (Box 68, Folder 1502)
  - New York State Thruway Authority, 17th Annual Report, December 31, 1966 (Box 68, Folder 1503)
  - New York State Mental Hygiene Facilities Improvement Fund, 1966 (Box 68, Folder 1504)
    Design Construction Report, January 9, 1967
  - New York State Housing Finance Agency, 1966 (Box 68, Folder 1505)
    Annual Report, January 30, 1967
  - President's Commission on Law Enforcement & Administration of Justice, February; 1967 (Box 68, Folder 1506)
  - New York State Science & Technology Foundation, 1966 (Box 68, Folder 1507)
    Annual Report, February 6, 1967
  - Transportation Bond Issue, March 7, 1967 (Box 68, Folder 1508)
  - Fire Insurance in Congested Areas, March 7, 1967 (Box 68, Folder 1509)
  - Statewide Outdoor Comprehensive Recreation Plan, Vol. 2, March 13, 1967 (Box 68, Folder 1510)
  - Jetports & General Aviation in the New York Metropolitan Area, March 16, 1967 (Box 68, Folder 1511)
  - Long Island Sound Crossings, March 16, 1967 (Box 68, Folder 1512)
  - Management & Development in New York State Departments & Agencies, May 1967 (Box 68, Folder 1513)
  - Blue Ribbon Panel Report on Municipal Hospitals of New York City, May 6, 1967 (Box 68, Folder 1514)
  - State Business Advisory Committee on Management Improvement, May 14, 1967 (Box 68, Folder 1515)
  - State Commission for Human Rights, Interim Report, June 26, 1967 (Box 68, Folder 1516)
  - New York State Identification & Intelligence System War Against Crime, July 18, 1967 (Box 68, Folder 1517)
  - Crime Victims Compensation Board, July 19, 1967 (Box 68, Folder 1518)
  - Proposed Adirondack Mountains National Park, July 30, 1967 (Box 68, Folder 1519)
  - Pure Waters Program Status Report, July 30, 1967 (Box 68, Folder 1520)
  - Narcotic Addiction Control Commission, Progress Report, August 7, 1967 (Box 68, Folder 1521)
  - The Urban Frontier, New York State Division of Housing & Community Renewal, August 10, 1967 (Box 69, Folder 1522)
  - Republican Governor's Association Policy Committee Action Plan: Social Injustice & Lawlessness, August 10, 1967 (Box 69, Folder 1523)
  - Plans for Marina & Boat Launching Site on the Hudson at Albany, August 31, 1967 (Box 69, Folder 1524)
  - Hudson River Lighthouses, Hudson River Valley Commission, September; 1967 (Box 69, Folder 1525)
  - Governor's Conference on Oceanography, October 12, 1967 (Box 69, Folder 1526)
  - Outdoor Recreation for the Physically Handicapped, October 16, 1967 (Box 69, Folder 1527)
  - State Commission for Human Rights, 1966 (Box 69, Folder 1528)
    Annual Report, October 28, 1967
  - New York State Natural Beauty Commission, 1966 (Box 69, Folder 1529)
    Annual Report, December, 1967
  - Statewide Comprehensive Outdoor Recreation Plan, Vol. 3, December 16, 1967 (Box 69, Folder 1530)
  - Governor's Electric Power Committee, December 20, 1967 (Box 69, Folder 1531)
  - Developing & managing the Water Resources of New York State, December 20, 1967 (Box 69, Folder 1532)
  - Fire Insurance in Congested Areas, 2nd Report, January 7, 1968 (Box 69, Folder 1533)
  - New York State Narcotic Addiction Control Commission, January 12, 1968 (Box 69, Folder 1534)
  - Study of Medicaid in New York State, January 12, 1968 (Box 69, Folder 1535)
  - Ad Hoc Committee Report on Medicaid, January 16, 1968 (Box 69, Folder 1536)
  - Mid-Crosstown Arterial Albany, January 25, 1968 (Box 69, Folder 1537)
  - The Adirondacks: New York's Forest Preserve & Proposed National Park, January 26, 1968 (Box 69, Folder 1538)
  - Select Committee on the Future of Private & Independent Higher Education in New York State, January 31, 1968 (Box 69, Folder 1539)
  - Select Committee on the Future of Private & Independent Higher Education in New York State, January 31, 1968 (Box 69, Folder 1540)
  - Doing Business with New York State, New York State Business Advisory Committee on Management Improvement, February 3, 1968 (Box 69, Folder 1541)
  - Flood Plain Management, New York State Water Resources Commission, February 24, 1968 (Box 69, Folder 1542)
  - Preserving Agricultural Land in New York State, February 27, 1968 (Box 69, Folder 1543)
  - Metropolitan Transportation: A Program for Improvement, February 28, 1968 (Box 69, Folder 1544)
  - New York State Science & Technology Foundation, 1967 (Box 69, Folder 1545)
    Annual Report, March 2, 1968
  - New York State Natural Beauty Commission Manual re: Regulation of Signs in Lake George, March 18, 1968 (Box 69, Folder 1546)
  - Ethnic & Racial Characteristics of Employees of New York State, 1st Annual Report, March 23, 1968 (Box 69, Folder 1547)
  - Review of Human Rights Laws & Procedures of New York State, March 27, 1968 (Box 69, Folder 1548)
  - Review of Human Rights Laws & Procedures of New York State, March 27, 1968 (Box 69, Folder 1549)
  - Governor's Commission Appointed to Review New York State's Abortion Law, March 30, 1968 (Box 70, Folder 1550)
  - Urban Development Corporation, April 23, 1968 (Box 70, Folder 1551)
  - Steering Committee of the Arden House Conference on Public Welfare, April 29, 1968 (Box 70, Folder 1552)
  - Challenge & Response, New York State Board of Social Welfare, May 1968 (Box 70, Folder 1553)
  - Job Opportunities for the Disadvantaged, May 10, 1968 (Box 70, Folder 1554)
  - Hudson River Expressway & Hudson River Expressway Park, New York State Department of Transportation, May 31, 1968 (Box 70, Folder 1555)
  - Governor's Committee on Public Employee Relations, Interim Report, June 17, 1968 (Box 70, Folder 1556)
  - Governor's Committee on Criminal Offenders, June 30, 1968 (Box 70, Folder 1557)
  - Mental Hygiene Facilities Improvement Fund, July 8, 1968 (Box 70, Folder 1558)
  - New York State Business Advisory Committee on Management Improvement, 2nd Annual Report, June 10, 1968 (Box 70, Folder 1559)
  - Summer & Seasonal Employment in State Agencies for Disadvantaged Youths, July 19, 1968 (Box 70, Folder 1560)
  - New York-Florida Interstate Opportunities Panel, July 26, 1968 (Box 70, Folder 1561)
  - Joint Legislative Committee on Motor Vehicles, Traffic & Highway Safety, December 1968 (Box 70, Folder 1562)
  - Municipal Police Training Council, Division for Local Police, December 5, 1968 (Box 70, Folder 1563)
  - Division of Housing & Community Renewal, Annual Report, December 5, 1968 (Box 70, Folder 1564)
  - Post Vietnam Planning Committee, December 18, 1968 (Box 70, Folder 1565)
  - Post Vietnam Planning Committee, December 18, 1968 (Box 70, Folder 1566)
  - Post Vietnam Planning Committee, December 18, 1968 (Box 70, Folder 1567)
  - Long Island Sound Crossings, December 27, 1968 (Box 70, Folder 1568)
  - Solving Problems of Healthcare, January 6, 1969 (Box 70, Folder 1569)
  - The Public Interest Now in Property & Liability Insurance Regulation, January 22, 1969 (Box 70, Folder 1570)
  - Governor's Committee on Public Employee Relations - Final Report, January 30, 1969 (Box 70, Folder 1571)
  - New York State Index of Federal & State Assistance Programs, February 5, 1969 (Box 70, Folder 1572)
  - The Fiscal Crisis in the Federal System Dramatized by Problems in Urban Areas, February 12, 1969 (Box 70, Folder 1573)
  - New York State Housing Finance Agency, 1968 (Box 70, Folder 1574)
    Annual Report, February 13, 1969
  - Special Committee on Vehicle Weights & Dimensions, February 24, 1969 (Box 70, Folder 1575)
  - New York State Science & Technology Foundation, 1968 (Box 70, Folder 1576)
    Annual Report, February 24, 1969
  - State Narcotics Commission, 1st 21 Months, February 26, 1969 (Box 70, Folder 1577)
  - Buffalo-Amherst Corridor Technical Report, March 1, 1969 (Box 70, Folder 1578)
  - State Aid to Local Government, Advisory Commission on Intergovernmental Relations, April; 1969 (Box 70, Folder 1579)
  - Special Committee on the Employment of Minority Groups in the News Media, April 8, 1969 (Box 70, Folder 1580)
  - New York-Florida Interstate Opportunities Panel, May 8, 1969 (Box 70, Folder 1581)
  - Manpower Needs for the Buffalo Construction Industry, June 20, 1969 (Box 70, Folder 1582)
  - Federal Navigation Projects in the Port of New York, July 8, 1969 (Box 70, Folder 1583)
  - New York Health & Mental Hygiene Facilities Improvement Corporation, September; 1969 (Box 70, Folder 1584)
  - Interdepartmental Committee on Migrant Workers, September 6, 1969 (Box 70, Folder 1585)
  - Division of Housing & Community Renewal, 1968-1969 (Box 70, Folder 1586)
    Annual Report, September 11, 1969
  - Abe Levine re: Lifeguard Strike at Palisades Interstate Park, October 10, 1969 (Box 71, Folder 1587)
  - New York State Police re: Development 1959-69, October 16, 1969 (Box 71, Folder 1588)
  - New York State Business Advisory Committee on Management Improvement, 3rd Annual Report, November 13, 1969 (Box 71, Folder 1589)
  - Governor's Committee to Study Per Capita Aid, December 6, 1969 (Box 71, Folder 1590)
  - Task Force on Administrative Adjudication of Traffic Violations, December 8, 1969 (Box 71, Folder 1591)
  - Special Commission on Ethical Standards in Public Service, December 12, 1969 (Box 71, Folder 1592)
  - Planning for Development in New York State, January 1970 (Box 71, Folder 1593)
  - New York State Housing Finance Agency, 1969 (Box 71, Folder 1594)
    Annual Report, January 28, 1970
  - Governor's Council on Drug Addiction, January 28, 1970 (Box 71, Folder 1595)
  - Temporary Commission to Study the Causes of Campus Unrest, 1st Report, February 1, 1970 (Box 71, Folder 1596)
  - State Council of Economic Advisors, 1st Annual Report, February 2, 1970 (Box 71, Folder 1597)
  - New York State Automobile Insurance System Changes, February 16, 1970 (Box 71, Folder 1598)
  - New York State Science & Technology Foundation, 1969 (Box 71, Folder 1599)
    Annual Report, February 20, 1970
  - Pure Waters Authority, 1969-1970 (Box 71, Folder 1600)
    Annual Report, April 30, 1970
  - New York State Advisory Council on Labor & Management Improper Practices Act, May 1, 1970 (Box 71, Folder 1601)
  - Joint Legislative Committee on Mass Transportation Report on New York State's Mobility, May 7, 1970 (Box 71, Folder 1602)
  - Review of Procedures of State University of New York (SUNY) & the State University Construction Fund, May 26, 1970 (Box 71, Folder 1603)
  - A Thermal Profile of the Waters of New York State, New York State Atomic & Space Development Authority, June; 1970 (Box 71, Folder 1604)
  - New York's Pure Water's Progress, June 12, 1970 (Box 71, Folder 1605)
  - Scenic & Recreational Development Hudson Riverfront Arterial, June 15, 1970 (Box 71, Folder 1606)
  - New York State Statistical Yearbook 1970, State Division of Budget, June 15, 1970 (Box 71, Folder 1607)
  - New York State Statistical Yearbook 1970, State Division of Budget, June 15, 1970 (Box 71, Folder 1608)
  - New York State Comprehensive Crime Control Plan, June 26, 1970 (Box 71, Folder 1609)
  - Hudson River Valley Commission, 1969 (Box 71, Folder 1610)
    Annual Report, July 8, 1970
  - New York State Department of Corrections, 1969 (Box 71, Folder 1611)
    Annual Report, July 13, 1970
  - State Office of Planning Coordination, 1969-1970 (Box 71, Folder 1612)
    Annual Report, September 8, 1970
  - Municipal Advisory Councils for Environmental Conservation, September 15, 1970 (Box 71, Folder 1613)
  - New York State Department of Environmental Conservation, First 100 Days, October 8, 1970 (Box 71, Folder 1614)
  - Occupations, Job Status & Ethnic Characteristics of Employees in New York State Agencies, 1970 (Box 71, Folder 1615)
    Annual Report, October 12, 1970
  - New York State Health & Mental Hygiene Facilities Improvement Corporation, Annual Report, November 1970 (Box 71, Folder 1616)
  - New York State Office for Community Affairs, 1969-1970 (Box 71, Folder 1617)
    Annual Report, November 9, 1970
  - Department of Agriculture & Markets, 1st Monthly Report, November 17, 1970 (Box 71, Folder 1618)
  - Rockefeller Roundup, December 1970 (Box 71, Folder 1619)
  - Abortions Performed in New York State, Preliminary Report, December 17, 1970 (Box 71, Folder 1620)
  - Temporary Study Commission on the Future of the Adirondacks, January 2, 1971 (Box 71, Folder 1621)
  - Governor's Committee to Study Per Capita Aid, Final Report, January 6, 1971 (Box 71, Folder 1622)
  - Community Antenna Television Systems, Public Service Commission, January 10, 1971 (Box 72, Folder 1623)
  - Community Antenna Television Systems, Public Service Commission, January 10, 1971 (Box 72, Folder 1624)
  - Community Antenna Television Systems, Public Service Commission, January 10, 1971 (Box 72, Folder 1625)
  - Marijuana: Temporary State Commission to Evaluate Drug Laws, Interim Report, January 25, 1971 (Box 72, Folder 1626)
  - Department of Housing & Finance, 1970 (Box 72, Folder 1627)
    Annual Report, January 28, 1971
  - New York State Development Plan 1, January 30, 1971 (Box 72, Folder 1628)
  - New York State Development Plan 1, January 30, 1971 (Box 72, Folder 1629)
  - New York State Development Plan 1, Regional Plans, January 30, 1971 (Box 72, Folder 1630)
  - State Commission on Eminent Domain, Interim Report, February 1, 1971 (Box 72, Folder 1631)
  - State Financial Assistance to Cultural Resources, March 1971 (Box 72, Folder 1632)
  - Social Services in New York State 1970, March 1971 (Box 72, Folder 1633)
  - New York State Commission to Commemorate the War of 1812 & the Composition of the Star-Spangled Banner, March 1, 1971 (Box 72, Folder 1634)
  - Temporary Commission to Study the Causes of Campus Unrest, 2nd Report, March 1, 1971 (Box 72, Folder 1635)
  - Temporary Commission to Study the Causes of Campus Unrest, 2nd Report, March 1, 1971 (Box 72, Folder 1636)
  - Comprehensive Crime Control Plan, March 19, 1971 (Box 72, Folder 1637)
  - The Needs of the Deaf & the Hearing Impaired, March 31, 1971 (Box 72, Folder 1638)
  - Temporary State Commission on Youth Education in Conservation, 2nd Report, March 31, 1971 (Box 72, Folder 1639)
  - Investigation of Drug Law Enforcement, Preliminary Report, April 4, 1971 (Box 72, Folder 1640)
  - Evaluation of Drug Laws, 2nd Interim Report, April 5, 1971 (Box 72, Folder 1641)
  - Governor's Steering Committee on Social Problems on Health & Hospital Services Costs, April 15, 1971 (Box 72, Folder 1642)
  - Governor's Steering Committee on Social Problems on Health & Hospital Services Costs, April 15, 1971 (Box 72, Folder 1643)
  - New York State Atomic & Space Development Authority re: Nuclear Power Plant Siting, April 22, 1971 (Box 72, Folder 1644)
  - Public Employment Relations Board, May 20, 1971 (Box 72, Folder 1645)
  - New York State Science & Technology Foundation, 1970 (Box 73, Folder 1646)
    Annual Report, June 18, 1971
  - Narcotic Addiction Control Commission on Drug Use in New York State, June 24, 1971 (Box 73, Folder 1647)
  - Department of Environmental Conservation, 1st Year Report, June 29, 1971 (Box 73, Folder 1648)
  - New York State Atomic & Space Development Authority, June 30, 1971 (Box 73, Folder 1649)
  - Financing Better Transportation for New York State, 1971 (Box 73, Folder 1650)
    Fact Book, July, 1971
  - Alcohol Abuse & Alcoholism in New York State, July 31, 1971 (Box 73, Folder 1651)
  - Alcohol Abuse & Alcoholism in New York State, July 31, 1971 (Box 73, Folder 1652)
  - Council of Economic Advisors, 1971 (Box 73, Folder 1653)
    Annual Report, August 4, 1971
  - Federal-State Partnership for National Health Insurance, November 8, 1971 (Box 73, Folder 1654)
  - A Child Advocacy System in New York State, November 30, 1971 (Box 73, Folder 1655)
  - People, Transportation & Jobs, Tri-State Regional Planning Commission Nassau & Suffolk County Report, December; 1971 (Box 73, Folder 1656)
  - Off-Track Pari-Mutual Betting Commission, February 1, 1972 (Box 73, Folder 1657)
  - The Compensation of Public Officials: Judges & Legislators, February 22, 1972 (Box 73, Folder 1658)
  - Financing Mass Transportation: A Positive Approach, April 1972 (Box 73, Folder 1659)
  - Temporary Commission on the Powers of Local Government, April 1972 (Box 73, Folder 1660)
  - Adirondack Park State Land Master Plan, June 1, 1972 (Box 73, Folder 1661)
  - Public Employment Relations Board Disclosure Report, June 29, 1972 (Box 73, Folder 1662)
  - Council of Economic Advisors, 1972 (Box 73, Folder 1663)
    Annual Report, August, 1972
  - Temporary Commission to Study the Causes of Campus Unrest, 3rd Report, December 28, 1972 (Box 73, Folder 1664)
  - Temporary Commission to Study the Causes of Campus Unrest, 3rd Report, December 28, 1972 (Box 73, Folder 1665)